https://www.passionroses.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Whether you are just surfing our site for inspiration and eye candy or buying the world’s most beautiful blooms, we appreciate the time you spend at passionroses.com. We want you to feel good about the time you spend with us and the information you share.
We know how important it is to feel safe and confident when you are on the intewebs!  Consider this the “fine print”, that part that no one ever reads and that we all agree to every time we do anything. It’s super important but not super fun.
The info provided by people like you help us personalize and elevate your experience here at PassionRoses.com  And our intent is always to provide a great experience, even in the fine print legal mumbo jumbo.
We know you care how information about you is used and shared. We appreciate your loyalty and trust. If you are still reading, buckle up, because this is the boring part and it’s not as pretty as looking at our roses. But we get it. So here we go:
We receive and store info you enter here. We do not share that information.  We receive and store “cookies” just like all the other sites you visit. You can disable cookies at any time but will not experience the full functionality of the website.  If cookies are disabled, we cannot recognize you as a registered user or have access to your account info. Cookies on our website last for one year. Cookies in our lunch room won’t make it through the day.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. Yes, on occasion we throw away cookies.
All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
From time to time we use third party tools for the purposes of analytics and marketing.
We also use a Gravitar (make this a clickable link to the privacy policy) service, so if you submit an approved comment, your Gravitar is visible to the public as well as your comment. Any submissions you make to us will retained.
Some articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
We may communicate with you through social media, email and other means that technology has only began to dream of. We may send you promotional messages about the best roses in the world and the encounters that people have with them.
If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from our emails, please do so at the link provided in the email. We will be sorry to see you go!
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. We don’t know why you would want to do this, but we aim to please, so whatever floats your boat. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.  We do not provide any of your non-public information (like your email address) to third parties without your consent, unless required by law.
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Nobody likes Spam. Except maybe Hawaii.
The information you provide is extremely important to us. Our intent is to guard and protect the security of this information during transmission by using encrypted security tools. We do so to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct usage of information. Just a heads up…to protect against unauthorized access to your password and computer, please be sure to sign off when you have finished using a shared computer.
In addition to any other legal or equitable remedies you encounter on our social media or this website, PassionRoses may, without prior notice to you, immediately terminate the Agreement or revoke any or all your rights granted under this Agreement. The provisions relating to Intellectual Property, Disclaimer, Limitation of Liability, Applicable Laws, Indemnification, and Severability shall survive any termination of this Agreement.
Users who access or use the Website from outside the United States are responsible for complying with their local laws and regulations.
THIS WEBSITE IS PRESENTED “AS IS” AND MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES, MISTAKES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. PASSIONRoses MAKES NO WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF THIS WEBSITE, OR AS TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR CONTENT OF ANY INFORMATION, SERVICE, OR MERCHANDISE PROVIDED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE. PRICE INFORMATION IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY AND COMPLETENESS OF ALL INFORMATION, OPINIONS AND OTHER MATERIAL ON THIS WEBSITE OR ANY SITES WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED. PASSIONRoses DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THIS WEBSITE CONTENT, THE RESULTS OF USE OF THE MATERIALS AVAILABLE ON THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING ITS AFFILIATES, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS, MERCHANTS, SPONSORS, LICENSORS AND THE LIKE, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS AND EMPLOYEES MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OR THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT, OR ANY OTHER PORTION OF THE WEBSITE OR SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNTS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR WARRANTIES ABOUT THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, OR TIMELINESS OF THE WEBSITE, SERVICES, GRAPHICS, OR LINKS UNLESS SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES THAT ARE NOT LEGALLY EXCLUDABLE UNDER ANY LAW. IN USING THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE THAT PASSIONRoses IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE, UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES, FOR ANY (a) INTERRUPTION OF BUSINESS; (b) ACCESS DELAYS OR ACCESS INTERRUPTIONS TO THE WEBSITE; (c) DATA NON-DELIVERY, MISDELIVERY, CORRUPTION, DESTRUCTION OR OTHER MODIFICATION; (d) LOSS OR DAMAGES OF ANY SORT INCURRED AS A RESULT OF DEALINGS WITH OR THE PRESENCE OF OFF-WEBSITE LINKS ON THE WEBSITE; (e) COMPUTER VIRUSES, SYSTEM FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION WHICH MAY OCCUR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING DURING HYPERLINK TO OR FROM THIRD PARTY WEBSITES; OR (f) EVENTS BEYOND OUR REASONABLE CONTROL. FURTHER, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, WE ARE NOT IN ANY WAY LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, OR ANY TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES (REGARDLESS OF THE FOUNDATION FOR THE ACTION) SHALL NOT EXCEED IN THE AGGREGATE THE AMOUNT OF FEES ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU TO PASSIONRoses THROUGH THE WEBSITE DURING THE MONTH IMMEDIATELY PRECEDING THE ACT ALLEGEDLY GIVING CAUSE TO ANY ALLEGED LIABILITY.
All laws of the State of Florida will govern these disclaimers, terms, and conditions. Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to the Website or social media shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in Miami-Dade County, Florida, except in regards to issues regarding violations of PASSIONRoses intellectual property rights, which we may seek relief from in any state or federal court of competent jurisdiction in the State of Florida. By using the Website or social media, you hereby consent to, and waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non-conveniences with respect to venue and jurisdiction in the state and federal courts of the State of Florida. Arbitration under this Agreement shall be conducted pursuant to the Commercial Arbitration Rules then prevailing at the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator’s award shall be final and binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under this Agreement shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to this Agreement, whether through class action proceedings or otherwise. In using this Website, you further agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of, related to, or connected with the use of this Website or Agreement must be filed within 1 year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever banned. By using this PASSIONRoses website or social media, you agree that PASSIONRoses remedy at law for any actual or threatened breach of this Agreement would be inadequate. As such, we shall be entitled to specific performance, injunctive relief, or both, in addition to any damages that we may be entitled to recover, along with reasonable expenses incurred by us for any form of dispute resolution, including, without limitation, attorneys’ fees. No right or remedy of PASSIONRoses shall be exclusive of any other, whether at law or in equity, including without limitation damages injunctive relief, attorneys’ fees and expenses. No instance of waiver by PASSIONRoses, of its rights, remedies under these terms and conditions shall imply any obligation to grant any similar, future, or another waiver.
In using this PASSIONRoses website and or social media, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless our officers, directors, affiliates and employees from any and all claims, liabilities, costs, and expenses, including, but not limited to, attorneys’ fees and expenses, arising in any way from or in connection with your use of this Website or any service available on or through this Website or our social media, including the uploading, posting, e-mailing, transmission, or infringement of any Content or other materials by you or users authorized by you, or any violation of these Terms and Conditions, our Privacy Policy or any other policy posted from time to time on the Website applicable to your use of the Website.
Shop
Rose Color Guide
About Us
Rose Care
My Account
My Shopping Cart
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Passion is only a phone call away!
